Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3, Section 3: Boxes 45-66
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3, Section 3: Boxes 45-66
- Box: 47, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: The Philip Morris Retirement Plan, 1966; Publication (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Item 8: The Philip Morris College Scholarship Plan, Publication (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Item 9: The Philip Morris Comprehensive Medical Plan, 1967; Publication (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Item 10: The Philip Morris Merit Award Program, Publication (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Item 11: Philip Morris Retirement Plan and Trust Agreement, Publication (Box 47, Folder 6)
- Box: 47, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Dedication Program, 1960; Publication (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: The First Asian Labor Leadership Institute, 1960; Publication (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: A Study Program for Free Trade Union Leaders In Asia Offered by The University of Philippines, Publication (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: The First Asian Labor Leadership Institute, 1960; Publication (Box 47, Folder 7)
- Box: 47, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Sickness Benefit Plan, 1960; Publication (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Marital Survivor Benefit Plan, 1961; Publication (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Gift and Contributory Group Insurance Plans, 1959; Publication (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: Vacation Plan, 1957; Publication (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: Sickness Benefits, 1974; Publication (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Item 6: Group Hospitalization and Surgical Benefit Plan; Major Medical Expense Insurance Plan, 1959; Publication (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Item 7: Gift and Contributory Group Life Insurance Plans, 1952; Publication (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Item 8: Sickness Benefit Plan, 1959; Publication (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Item 9: Welcome to Peoples Gas, Publication (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Item 10: Vacation Plan, 1949; Publication (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Item 11: Vacation Plan, 1974; Publication (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Item 12: Vacation Plan, 1965; Publication (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Item 13: Group Term Life Insurance Plans, 1974; Publication (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Item 14: Comprehensive Medical Plan, 1974; Publication (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Item 15: Comprehensive Medical Plan, 1974; Publication (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Item 16: Employee Stock Purchase Plan, 1961; Publication (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Item 17: Group Hospitalization and Surgical Benefit Plan, 1953; Publication (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Item 18: Group Hospitalization and Surgical Benefit Plan; Major Medical Expense Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 47, Folder 8)
- Box: 47, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Service Annuity System, 1959; Publication (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: Our Pension Plan, 1959; Publication (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: Answers to Your Pension Questions, 1950; Publication (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: Service Annuity System, 1951; Publication (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: Termination Allowance Plan, 1958; Publication (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Item 6: Employee Handbook, 1962; Publication (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Item 7: Employee Safety Manual, 1974; Publication (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Item 8: Record of Employee Service, Publication (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Item 9: Regulations for Determining "Service", 1949; Publication (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Item 10: Suggestion System, 1967; Publication (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Item 11: Here's How to Use Your Suggestion System, Publication (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Item 12: We...The Peoples Gas Light and Coke Company, Publication (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Item 13: Discussion of Company's Financial Position With Supervisory Employees, 1948; Publication (Box 47, Folder 9)
    Author: Mr. James F. Oates, Jr.
  - Item 14: Checklist of Material Needed On Company Industrial Relations Activities, 1963; Publication (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Item 15: Documentary Materials On File at the industrial Relations Section, Publication (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Item 16: Checklist of Materials Needed on Company Industrial Relations Activities, 1959; Publication (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Item 17: Checklist of Materials Needed on Company Industrial Relations Activities, Publication (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Item 18: Documentary Material On File at the Industrial Relations Section, Publication (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Item 19: Documentary Material On File at the Industrial Relations Section, Publication (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Item 20: 1948 Dinner Quarter Century Club of The Peoples Gas Light and Coke Company, Publication (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Item 21: To All Employees:, 1948; Publication (Box 47, Folder 9)
    Author: James F. Oates, Jr.
  - Item 22: Selected Sections of Manual of Job Evaluation, Publication (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Item 23: Employment Tests for Meter Readers, Publication (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Item 24: Planning: Management Manual, Publication (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Item 25: Improving Work Methods Part I: Selecting Jobs For Work Improvement, Publication (Box 47, Folder 9)
- Box: 47, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Personnel Record, Publication (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: Employment Policy, 1972; Publication (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: Employment Policy, 1972; Publication (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Item 4: Affirmative Action Program, 1973; Publication (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Item 5: Affirmative Action Program, 1973; Publication (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Item 6: Affirmative Action Program, 1973; Publication (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Item 7: Affirmative Action Program, 1973; Publication (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Item 8: Affirmative Action Program, 1973; Publication (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Item 9: Employee Safety, 1974; Publication (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Item 10: Salary Increase Policy During The First year of Employment for Employees in the Clerical Compensation Structure, 1975; Publication (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Item 11: Salary Increase Policy During The First year of Employment for Employees in the Clerical Compensation Structure, 1975; Publication (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Item 12: Merit and Promotional Increase Policy for Employees in the Clerical Compensation Structure, 1975; Publication (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Item 13: Merit and Promotional Increase Polity for Employees in the Clerical Compensation Structure, 1975; Publication (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Item 14: Merit and Promotional Increase Policy for Management Employees, 1976; Publication (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Item 15: Merit and Promotional Increase Policy for Management Employees, 1976; Publication (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Item 16: Merit and Promotional Increase Policy for Management Employees, 1976; Publication (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Item 17: Shift Premium Payment, 1974; Publication (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Item 18: Merit and Promotional Increase Policy for Executive Management Employees, 1976; Publication (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Item 19: Merit and Promotional Increase Policy for Executive Management Employees, 1976; Publication (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Item 20: Merit and Promotional Increase Policy for Executive Management Employees, 1976; Publication (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Item 21: Air Transportation, 1973; Publication (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Item 22: Air Transportation, 1973; Publication (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Item 23: Reimbursable Expenses, 1975; Publication (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Item 24: Reimbursable Expenses, 1975; Publication (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Item 25: Reimbursable Expenses, 1975; Publication (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Item 26: Reimbursable Expenses, 1975; Publication (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Item 27: Reimbursable Expenses, 1975; Publication (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Item 28: Reimbursable Expenses, 1975; Publication (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Item 29: Office Hours, 1975; Publication (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Item 30: Daylight Saving Schedule, 1975; Publication (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Item 31: Observance of Holidays, 1975; Publication (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Item 32: Alcoholism and Drug Abuse, 1974; Publication (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Item 33: Dedication Plaque In Honor of Employees Who Died in World War II, Publication (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Item 34: Summary Record Card or "Kardex", Publication (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Item 35: Employment Registration Card, Publication (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Item 36: Employment Application, Publication (Box 47, Folder 11)
- Box: 47, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Hazardous Materials Regulations, 1969; Publication (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: Policy on Alcoholism and for Guidance in Handling Alcoholism, Publication (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Item 3: Penn Central Supplemental Pension Plan for employees in non-agreement positions, Publication (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Item 4: Supervisors' Manual of Procedures for Obtaining Medical Service and for the Handling of Injured Employees and Those Absent for Medical Reasons, Publication (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Item 5: Upward potential: handbook for Supervisors and Managers, 1975; Publication (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Item 6: College Recruitment Procedures Guide, Publication (Box 47, Folder 12)
- Box: 47, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Freight Divisions, Publication (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Item 2: Freight Rates, 1970; Publication (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Item 3: Freight Rates, 1970; Publication (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Item 4: Freight Rates, 1970; Publication (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Item 5: Freight Rates, 1970; Publication (Box 47, Folder 13)
- Box: 47, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Group Comprehensive Medical Insurance Protection for Employees if Phillips Petroleum Company, 1959; Publication (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Item 2: You and Phillips 66, 1966; Publication (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Item 3: You and Phillips 66, 1956; Publication (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Item 4: You and Phillips 66, 1962; Publication (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Item 5: An Oilman's Glimpse at the Next 100 Years, 1966; Publication (Box 47, Folder 15)
    Author: Stanley Learned
  - Item 6: Evaluating Your Job, 1952; Publication (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Item 7: Group Comprehensive Medical Insurance Protection, 1966; Publication (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Item 8: Group Life and Total-Permanent Disability Insurance, 1957; Publication (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Item 9: Your Health and Accident Insurance Plan, 1955; Publication (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Item 10: Group Life and Total Permanent Disability Insurance, 1962; Publication (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Item 11: Group Comprehensive Medical Insurance Protection for Employees of Phillips 66, 1962; Publication (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Item 12: Group Life and Total-Permanent Disability Insurance, 1961; Publication (Box 47, Folder 15)
- Box: 47, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Federal ControlThe Sugar-Coated Route to Less Natural Gas at Higher Prices, 1951; Publication (Box 47, Folder 16)
    Author: K.S. Adams
  - Item 2: Your Suggestion Plan, 1961; Publication (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Item 3: Counsel for the Young Engineer, Publication (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Item 4: Your Retirement Income plan, 1960; Publication (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Item 5: Your Thrift Plan as Amended, 1955; Publication (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Item 6: Your Thrift Plan as Amended, 1955; Publication (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Item 7: Your Retirement Income Plan, 1955; Publication (Box 47, Folder 16)
- Box: 47, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Qualification Record, Publication (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Item 2: Qualification Record, Publication (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Item 3: Qualification Record, Publication (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Item 4: Qualification Record, Publication (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Item 5: Qualification Record, Publication (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Item 6: Qualification Record, Publication (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Item 7: Qualification Record, Publication (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Item 8: Qualification Record, Publication (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Item 9: Phillips Petroleum Company, Publication (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Item 10: Phillips Petroleum Company, Publication (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Item 11: Bartlesville, Oklahoma Home of Phillips Petroleum Company, Publication (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Item 12: Phillips Petroleum Company and Subsidiaries Principal Domestic Operations, Publication (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Item 13: Phillips Petroleum Company and Subsidiaries International Operations, Publication (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Item 14: Phillips "Firsts", Publication (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Item 15: Phillips Research, Publication (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Item 16: Phillips Research, Publication (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Item 17: Phillips Research Center, Bartlesville, Oklahoma, Publication (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Item 18: Chemical Operations, Publication (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Item 19: Chemical Operations, Publication (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Item 20: Chemical Operations, Publication (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Item 21: Chemical Operations, Publication (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Item 22: Phillips Chemical Manufacturing Plants - Domestic, Publication (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Item 23: Phillips Chemical Manufacturing Plants - Outside U.S., Publication (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Item 24: Plastic and Other Finished Products Fabricators, Publication (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Item 25: Phillips Natural Gas Operations, Publication (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Item 26: Natural Gas Operations, Publication (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Item 27: Phillips Operations for Extraction of Natural Gas Liquids, Publication (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Item 28: Phillips Natural Gasoline Plants, Publication (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Item 29: Phillips Natural Gasoline Plants - U.S., Publication (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Item 30: Natural Gasoline Plants - Outside U.S., Publication (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Item 31: Phillips Refineries, Publication (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Item 32: International Activities, Publication (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Item 33: International Activities, Publication (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Item 34: International Activities, Publication (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Item 35: Countries or Areas Outside U.S. Where Phillips Produces or Has Reserves, Publication (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Item 36: Countries Having Phillips Licensee Plants, Publication (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Item 37: Countries Where Phillips Markets Products, Publication (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Item 38: Borgerm Texas, Area, Publication (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Item 39: Borger, Texas, Publication (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Item 40: Borger Crude Oil Processing Facilities, Publication (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Item 41: Borger Natural Gas Liquids Facilities, Publication (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Item 42: Philblack Plant, Publication (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Item 43: Philtex Chemical Plant, Publication (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Item 44: Copolymer Plant, Publication (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Item 45: Plains Butadiene Plant, Publication (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Item 46: Houston - Sweeney, Texas, Area, Publication (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Item 47: Adams Terminal on the Houston Ship Channel, Publication (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Item 48: Echo Philblack Plant, Publication (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Item 49: Phillips Principal Sales Offices, Publication (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Item 50: Petroleum Marketing Terminals - U.S., Publication (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Item 51: Light Oil and Lube Oil Terminals and Bulk Plants in Operation, Publication (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Item 52: Phillips Producing States, Publication (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Item 53: Thrift Plan of Phillips Petroleum Company and Subsidiary Companies, 1953; Publication (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Item 54: Sheet 1, 1967; Publication (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Item 55: Career Opportunities in Manufacturing Department, Publication (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Item 56: Phillips Petroleum Company, Publication (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Item 57: Phillips Petroleum Company, Publication (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Item 58: Phillips Petroleum Company, Publication (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Item 59: Phillips Petroleum Company, Publication (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Item 60: Phillips Petroleum Company, Publication (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Item 61: Qualification Record, Publication (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Item 62: Qualification Record, Publication (Box 47, Folder 17)
- Box: 47, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Some Highlights of Phillips Petroleum Company, Publication (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Item 2: Research and Development, Publication (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Item 3: All-weather drilling platform erected in Alaska's Cook Inlet, Publication (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Item 4: Phillips Research Center, Bartlesville, Oklahoma, Publication (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Item 5: Atomic Energy Division, Publication (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Item 6: The Cooperative Education Program at Phillips Petroleum Company, Publication (Box 47, Folder 18)
- Box: 47, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Department Heads, Supervisors, and Other Management Personnel, 1962; Publication (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Item 2: Approved Employee Relations Policies Manual, Publication (Box 47, Folder 19)
- Box: 47, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Approved Employee Relations Policies Manual, Publication (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - Item 2: Department Heads, Supervisors, and Other Management Personnel, 1951; Publication (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - Item 3: Index, 1952; Publication (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - Item 4: Approved Employee Relations Policies Manual, Publication (Box 47, Folder 20)
- Box: 47, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Approved Employee Relations Policies Manual, Publication (Box 47, Folder 21)
- Box: 47, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 47, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Approved Policies Pertaining to Personnel & Employee Relations, Publication (Box 47, Folder 22)
- Box: 48, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Retirement Program for Salaried Employees, 1959; Publication (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Retirement Program for Salaried Employees, 1959; Publication (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Let's Talk about Confidence, Security, & Peace-of-Mind, Publication (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Income Protection Program, 1964; Publication (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Your Pillsbury Group Insurance Program, Publication (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Salesman Rating Report, Publication (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Sales Management Analysis, Publication (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Box: 48, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Dartnell Industrial Relations Service, Publication (Box 48, Folder 2)
- Box: 48, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Employees' Retirement Income Plan, 1961; Publication (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Employees' Profit-Sharing Plan, 1956; Publication (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: A Company Manual, 1970; Publication (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Payroll Deduction Personal Insurance Program, Publication (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Employees and Dependents Group Life Insurance Plan, 1970; Publication (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Handbook of the Pitney Bowes Employees' Federal Credit Union, 1971; Publication (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: Employees' Stock Purchase Plan, 1957; Publication (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: A Scholarship Program for Sons and Daughters of Employees of Pitney-Bowes, Inc. and Pitney-Bowes of Canada, Ltd., 1960; Publication (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: S Scholarship Program for Sons and Daughters, 1964; Publication (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: For Employees' Comprehensive Medical Expense Plan, 1960; Publication (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Item 11: Handbook of the Pitney-Bowes Employees' Federal Credit Union, 1961; Publication (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Item 12: Life Insurance Plan, 1962; Publication (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Item 13: What is the Credit Union?, 1959; Publication (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Item 14: Home News for Pitney-Bowes' G.I.'s, Publication (Box 48, Folder 3)
- Box: 48, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Management Conferences, 1953; Publication (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Sample Agenda - CPR Section Meeting, 1954; Publication (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Six Main Uses of Questions In Directing Discussion, Publication (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Four Basic Types of Questions, Publication (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Two Rules for Using Questions, Publication (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Management Conferences - Report and Summary, 1954; Publication (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: Management Conferences, 1954; Publication (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: Management Conferences - Report and Summary, 1954; Publication (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: Management Conferences, 1954; Publication (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: Employee Performance Rating, 1954; Publication (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Item 11: Management Conferences, 1954; Publication (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Item 12: Management Conferences, 1954; Publication (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Item 13: Management Conferences, 1954; Publication (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Item 14: Management Conferences, 1954; Publication (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Item 15: Management Conferences, 1954; Publication (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Item 16: Management Conferences, 1954; Publication (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Item 17: Management Conferences, 1954; Publication (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Item 18: Management Conferences, 1954; Publication (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Item 19: A Performance Review of, Publication (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Item 20: A Performance Review of, Publication (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Item 21: The Introduction and Interpretation of a Profit Sharing Plan, 1953; Publication (Box 48, Folder 4)
    Author: Walter H. Wheeler, Jr.
  - Item 22: Case Studies in Applying Standard Data to office Incentives, 1954; Publication (Box 48, Folder 4)
    Author: W. Gilbert Brooks
  - Item 23: A Review of the Service of, Publication (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Item 24: A Performance Review of, Publication (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Item 25: A Performance Review of, Publication (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Item 26: The Effect of Pitney-Bowes Wage-And-Salary Dividends on Compensation, Assuming an Annual Dividend Rate of 6%, Publication (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Item 27: A Performance Review, Publication (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Item 28: PB Time Study, Publication (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Item 29: Employees' Profit-Sharing Plan, 1965; Publication (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Item 30: The Exchange, 1953; Publication (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Item 31: Apprenticeship Standards, Publication (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Item 32: Management Conferences, Publication (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Item 33: Management Conferences, Publication (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Item 34: Management Conferences, 1953; Publication (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Item 35: Management Conferences, 1953; Publication (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Item 36: Management Conferences, 1953; Publication (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Item 37: Management Conferences, 1953; Publication (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Item 38: Management Conferences, 1953; Publication (Box 48, Folder 4)
- Box: 48, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Your Blue Cross and Blue Shield Plan, 1955; Publication (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Your Pension Plan, Publication (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Your Group Insurance Plan, 1955; Publication (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Conference Leadership Operation Facts, 1955; Publication (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Box: 48, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Evaluating Your Job, 1952; Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Group Life and Total-Permanent Disability Insurance, 1954; Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Your Health and Accident Insurance Plan, 1952; Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Handbook of Safety Rules for Station and Terminal Employees, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: Group Life and Total-Permanent Disability Insurance, 1952; Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)